{
    "id": "bfdaf8d910744969919fd80f757e2e53",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. her fiancé at a library.",
            "description": "Met is the past simple form of meet.",
            "answers": [
                "meet",
                "meeted",
                "met"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6bde1750335409681f301a517bd8665"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. some apples yesterday.",
            "description": "Bought is the past simple form of buy.",
            "answers": [
                "buyed",
                "bought",
                "buy"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "02f92fddff7044ca9ee7eadfa37f939c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. to remain a spinster.",
            "description": "Chose is the past simple form of choose. ",
            "answers": [
                "choose",
                "choosed",
                "chose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6dbaca724df140deb9f3f8f8a14dd3ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat ……………………… out of the window.",
            "description": "Ran is the past simple form of run.",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "runned",
                "ran"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0d1db8f6529f408f9b2bc1854571815c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… a terrible experience yesterday.",
            "description": "Had is the past simple form of have. ",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "have had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e0c6bb288dbe4a98a35a41ed6c3d3942"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. across the river.",
            "description": "Swam is the past simple form of swim. ",
            "answers": [
                "swam",
                "swimmed",
                "swamed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d9f9a0938d64f889e4494d77fc1f4b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… around but I ……………………… anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "turn, didn't saw",
                "turned, didn't see",
                "turned, didn't saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0e415103fce49a980465fc3f8b8b009"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. in a low voice.",
            "description": "Spoke is the past simple form of speak.",
            "answers": [
                "speaked",
                "spoke",
                "spoked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "442b43c6dc6643ea9a8e9e1a897b3f0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… the vase accidentally.",
            "description": "Broke is the past simple form of break.",
            "answers": [
                "breaked",
                "brock",
                "broke"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "15cc99407fa541e7afe04ddcd8b9ffed"
        },
        {
            "question": "The bird ………………………… away.",
            "description": "Flew is the past simple form of fly. ",
            "answers": [
                "flied",
                "flew",
                "flyed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "543802a90b3446c9ba78ff1a70d64ba2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… the vegetables with a knife.",
            "description": "Cut is the past and past participle form of cut. ",
            "answers": [
                "cut",
                "cutted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05ea1bab19a940c79868a64581834df5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. the candle out.",
            "description": "Blew is the past simple form of blow. ",
            "answers": [
                "blowed",
                "blew",
                "blewed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "37907ae32a6440dea38323e424c0a967"
        }
    ]
}